Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) Records
Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) Records
- Publications
  - William Pearson Tolley Medal series (WPT)
    - WPT3 Universities, Adult Education and Social Criticism (Raybould, Sidney Griffith), 1970 (Box 17)
    - WPT4 Towards Still Greater Professionalism (Bartlett, Kenneth G.), 1971 (Box 17)
    - WPT5 Relentless Verity: Education for Being-Becoming-Belonging (Kidd, James Robbins), 1973 (Box 17)
    - WPT6 "A Rusty Person is Worse Than Rusty Iron" -- Adult Education and the Development of Africa (Bown, Lalage), 1975 (Box 17)
    - WPT7 The Promise and Pragmatism of Adult Education (White, Thurman), 1979 (Box 17)
- Administrative files
  - 1966-1982, 5 folders (Box 17)
  - "Accent on Social Philosophy", 1974-1975 (Box 17)
  - Adult Education Association, 1970-1976 (Box 17)
  - Adult Education Clearinghouse, 1964-1974 (Box 17)
  - ACHE, NAPCAE, NEA, 1970 (Box 17)
  - Apps, Jerrold, 1973-1976 (Box 17)
  - Autographs, 1972-1973 (Box 17)
  - Bartlett, Kenneth G., 1971-1972 (Box 17)
  - Bown, Lalage, 1975-1976 (Box 17)
  - Carlson, Robert A., 1969-1974 (Box 17)
  - Chicago Tribune, 1972-1975 (Box 17)
  - CPAE, 1972-1973 (Box 17)
  - Correspondence
    - 1965-1984, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Carbons, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Mailings, 1970-1974 (Box 17)
    - Doris Chertow, 1974-1975 (Box 17)
    - Crime Book, 1969 (Box 17)
    - Dubnick, Phyllis (Box 17)
    - Krinsky, Fred, 1971-1972 (Box 17)
    - Schwartz, Harry, 1969-1970 (Box 17)
  - Council on Continuing Education, 1973 (Box 17)
  - Cross, Wilbur, 1973-1976 (Box 17)
  - Darkenwald, Beder, Merozow, 1974 (Box 17)
  - Discussion leadership guide - inquiries (Box 18)
  - Dissertation abstracts, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Distribution contracts, 1968-1971 (Box 18)
  - Even, Mary Jane, 1973-1976 (Box 18)
  - "Evolution of Man" - contract agreement (Box 18)
  - "Evolution of Man" - correspondence, 1966-1971 (Box 18)
    See also Publications: American Foundation for Continuing Education (AFCE) series (AFC): AFC68 Evolution of Man
  - "Exploring the Universe" - correspondence, 1960-1972; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - "Exploring the Universe" - permissions (Box 18)
  - "Exploring the Universe" - photograph permissions (Box 18)
  - Form letters, 1973-1974 (Box 18)
  - "Future of Religion", 1972 (Box 18)
  - "Great Issues in American Politics", 1967-1970 (Box 18)
    See also Publications: American Foundation for Continuing Education (AFCE) series (AFC): AFC33 Great Issues in American Politics Part I; Publications: Fund for Adult Education series (FAE): FAE30 Great Issues in American Politics Part I
  - Greer, Loyal, 1974-1977 (Box 18)
  - Houle, Cyril O., 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - I.B.M., 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Inventories, 1968-1978 (Box 18)
  - Jacobson, Nolan Pliny, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Jessup, Frank, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - Kozoll, Charles, 1970-1972 (Box 18)
  - "List of Publications," Charters, Alexander N. and Holmwood, Donald [same as MSS26], 1983 (Box 18)
  - Manuscripts
    - "Concerns About Adult Education" (Schroeder, Wayne) (Box 18)
    - "New Media", 1968 (Box 18)
    - "Why Adults Learn" (Tough, Allen) (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - Memos, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Memos from Alexander N. Charters, 1972-1976 (Box 18)
  - "Memo from Syracuse", 1972-1976 (Box 18)
  - Miller, Paul, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Moses, Stanley, 1971-1973 (Box 18)
  - "Mystery of Matter" - records and permissions, 1963-1971 (Box 18)
  - National Institute for Adult Education - England (NIAE), 1968; 1973 (Box 18)
  - New York Associaton for Continuing Education (NYACE), 1969-1975 (Box 18)
  - Non-profit corporation reports, 1964-1969; includes articles of incorporation (Box 19)
  - Office procedures, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Ohliger, John, 1971-1975 (Box 19)
  - Organizer's manual, AFCE, 1962 (Box 19)
  - Oxford Press projects, 1966-1973 (Box 19)
  - Pardoen, Alan R., 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Penfield, Kathleen, 1973-1974 (Box 19)
  - Peters, John M., 1975-1977 (Box 19)
  - Problems, 1977-1978 (Box 19)
  - Publications
    - 1966-1980, 6 folders (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1979; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Form letters, 1977-1978 (Box 19)
  - Raybould, Sidney G., 1970 (Box 19)
  - Readings in American foreign policy, 1958-1960; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Readings in world politics (Box 19)
  - Records (financial), 1970-1977 (Box 19)
  - Redman, George, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Rivera, William, 1992; curriculum vitae, summary of professional experience (Box 19)
  - School of Education minutes, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Science and international relations
    - Carnegie endowment, 1965; 1968 (Box 19)
    - Permissions, 1967-1971 (Box 19)
    - Working papers, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Science and public policy - correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 20)
  - Science and world affairs
    - Biographies (Box 20)
    - Illustrations (Box 20)
    - Reading lists (Box 20)
  - "Ways of Mankind" (Box 20)
  - Whipple, James, 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Young, Louise, correspondence (Box 20)
- Syracuse University Resources for Educators of Adults (SUREA)
  - Annual report, 1980 (Box 20)
  - Collection descriptions and lists (Box 20)
  - Descriptive subject headings (Box 20)
  - Drafts, 1988-1989; annotated draft of a description of the adult education collections -- possibly an early draft of MSS34 which was later split into several different MSS series publications; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - General correspondence, 1973-1987; 5 folders (Box 20)
  - Memos
    - SU-AE Memo nos. 1-76, 3 folders (Box 20)
    - SUREA Memo nos. 1-9 (Box 20)
  - National Center for Higher Education Management Systems, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Notes (Alexander N. Charters), undated (Box 20)
  - Printed material (Box 20)
  - Stensland, Per Gustaf (Box 20)
  - SUPCE, SUREA statements (Box 20)
  - Syracuse University Libraries, 1979-1987; correspondence with library personnel regarding donors, gifts, cataloguing, and other matters related to the adult education collections; 2 folders (Box 20)